wehoville.com 2018-10-29

# WEHOville | Privacy Policy

**(Effective date: August 7, 2013; revised Jan. 2, 2016)**

WEHOville.com, a property of WHMC LLC, greatly values the privacy of its readers and contributors (collectively, the “Users”) and is committed to protecting that privacy. WEHOville also values the work and contributions of freelance writers and op-ed writers and its own staff and has established rules governing how that work can be used by other entities.

We have prepared this Privacy & Terms of Use Policy to help you understand more about how we collect, use, and disclose information that we collect about consumers through our web.

This Privacy & Terms of Use Policy describes the practices that WHMC follows with respect to the collection, maintenance and use of information submitted on WEHOville.com (the “Site”).

This Privacy & Terms of Use  Policy applies only to information we collect from  and publish on this Site, and does not apply to any other website or business activity of WHMC. Also, this  Policy does not cover information that you voluntarily make public, such as by posting it in a publicly accessible place on the Internet. Please read all of the terms below carefully before using the Site.

By using the Site, and/or providing information to us, you consent to the collection, maintenance and use of this information by us. Your use of the Site indicates your agreement to abide by the terms in effect.

We reserve the right to modify or amend the terms of this  Policy from time to time. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms means that you accept those changes. We will give you notice of the revised Policy by posting the revised policy on the Site and by revising the “effective date” set forth above.

### Information We Collect

We collect information from our Users at several different points and in several ways on the Site:

 **Information that you provide.  **We may collect information that you choose to provide to us (including in comments or other user content that you submit to us or when you subscribe to our services). This may include information such as your name, e-mail address, phone number, year of birth, gender, zip code, country, postal address, credit card number or other billing information, user name, password, and password reminder questions and answers. We may ask you for information when you register or subscribe, or at other times—such as when you enter a contest or participate in a promotion, when you provide content, or when you order products from us. The User is not required to participate or disclose any information. Users’ personally identifiable information is not shared with other organizations without notice and choice. In the cases in which we use a third party to conduct surveys and contests, the third party may not use Users’ personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

  *  **Automated information.** Using technologies that are widely used on the Internet, such as cookies, web beacons, and other technologies, we also may automatically collect information about your computer or mobile device and online activity when you access the Site via a web browser through our web server (which may be hosted by a third party). For example, when you visit WEHOville.com, we may collect your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type and operating system, as well as information about which pages you visit and the page, if any, that referred you to our sites or that you visit after our sites. This information is used primarily to discover which features users are reading the most, what features they like best and what we can do to make things better. We currently use, or may use, such information in various ways:

  *  **Cookies:** This Site uses “cookies.” “Cookies” are small text files that allow websites to store and retrieve information about you from your computer system. We use this information for a variety of purposes, such as to remember you when you return to our websites or to identify your activities as you use certain parts of the Site. To do this, we may store a unique identifier on your computer or device. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but you may not be able to take full advantage of our Site’s features if you do. We do not and cannot use cookies or IP address tracking to retrieve personally identifiable information from your computer.

  *  **Log files:** Like most standard web site servers we use log files. This includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track User’s movement in the aggregate and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze User movement. **  
**

  * **Web beacons:** We or our third-party partners also may use technologies called web beacons, which provide website operators and third parties a means to deliver a graphic image on a web page or in an email message for the purpose of gathering data. We and our partners use web beacons for a variety of purposes, including analyzing the use of the Site and in conjunction with cookies to provide content and ads that are more relevant to you. **  
**

### Targeted Advertising

WEHOville.com may tailor advertisements on the Site to a user’s apparent interests, based on user browsing activity. That is, ads may be displayed for you on the Site based on the pages and content that you view. This is sometimes known as first-party online behavioral advertising. Also, your viewing activity on the Site may be shared with advertising networks, so that they can display ads for you, which they believe will interest you, on other sites, not affiliated with WEHOville.com. This is sometimes known as third-party online behavioral advertising:

  *  **Third-Party Advertisers:** Information about your visits to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad, is aggregated and used to serve ads to you. If you would prefer not to receive advertisements through the Site that are targeted to your interests, you can inform our advertising vendor, Google, Inc., of your preference by clicking the “Opt out” button at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. You also can manage your advertising preferences at <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>.

In some cases, we and advertisers on the Site work with other third-party vendors to help deliver advertisements targeted to your interests. These vendors include ad networks and analytics providers, and they use cookies or other technologies to collect information about your online activity (e.g., the sites and pages you have visited) in order to help advertisers deliver particular ads that they believe you would find most relevant. Many third-party vendors that perform these functions are members of the Network Advertising Initiative or the Digital Advertising Alliance, and you can opt out of those vendors’ delivery of targeted advertising to you by visiting <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> and [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)

Please note that, because these opt-out tools will place a cookie on your computer to record your opt-out preference, any actions you take using these tools will apply only to the web browser that you use to take the action. Also, these tools may not work as expected if you set your browser to refuse cookies.

### Use and Disclosure of Information

We maintain and use personally identifiable information for the purpose or purposes for which it is provided and for purposes specified in this  Policy. For example, we may maintain and use personally identifiable information to send newsletters and messages that you have opted to receive; to establish your online account and recognize you when you return to the Site; to contact you regarding contests, promotions, polls, and surveys; to provide customer support; or to otherwise communicate with you regarding our Site, an ad you posted, an event you submitted to the Site, or your comments or letters to the editor.

We may also maintain and use your personally identifiable information to attribute your comments, letters to the editor and/or other submissions to the Site to you. We may require that you supply certain information to us (such as your real name, daytime telephone number and/or e-mail address) in connection with comments and other submissions to the Site. That is because we may need to contact you, and because your identity may be important to understand your point of view. If you send us comments or other submissions, we reserve the right to publish them in print or display them on this Site in full or in edited form.

We may combine personally identifiable information and automatic information we obtain from you or your activities with other data concerning or relating to the behavioral and demographic attributes of our customers, in order to identify our best customers, reach them effectively, understand their interests and best manage our relationships with them.

We may also use personally identifiable information to send you advertisements, promotions and information about the Site and our partners.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may have breached our Terms of Use or who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other users of our Site, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose personally identifiable information when we reasonably believe that the law requires it.

If you chose to provide your personally identifiable information for the purposes of a third-party contest, promotion, poll, survey or newsletter, your personally identifiable information will be given to the Site and to the third-party advertiser/sponsor involved with the relevant contest, promotion, poll, survey or newsletter and/or its agents and affiliates.

We occasionally have third party agents, subsidiaries, affiliates and joint ventures that perform functions on our behalf, such as credit card processing, shipping or stocking orders, providing customer service, data combination, etc. They are provided access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions (but these service providers are not permitted to use personally identifiable information that we provide for any purpose other than to provide service to us).

We may maintain and use automatic information to track how our visitors use the Site, study traffic patterns, and run and maintain the site, and we and other third parties may provide targeted advertisements to you based on such data.

We may share aggregated data with our advertisers and other marketing and business partners.

This  Policy does not apply to any information you choose to make public.

### Links

This Site provides links to websites maintained by other organizations. WEHOville.com provides these links as a convenience to users, but it does not operate, control or endorse such sites. WEHOville.com also disclaims any responsibility for the information on those sites and any products or services offered on such sites. Please review the privacy policies of these sites.

### Reuse of WEHOville Content

All content published on WEHOville.com, with the exception of that content attributed solely to City News Service and that content that is identified in quotation marks as coming from another publication, is the exclusive property of WHMC LLC and cannot be republished by any other person or organization or business unless that person or organization or business cites WEHOville.com as the source of that content, provides a direct link to that content on WEHOville.com and limits the content used from WEHOville.com to no more than 50 words.

### Children

Some of the material on this Site is for mature audiences, and parents and guardians should take responsibility for monitoring their children’s use of the Site. Children under the age of 13 should not use this Site. We do not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from users of the Site who are under the age of thirteen.

### Questions?

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, you may contact us at: henry@wehoville.com.
